<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Zen Garden (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.ZenGarden</packageId>
  <author>cuproPanda</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/ZenGarden</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of cuproPandas mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1221867010
based on mantrasongs updated version
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1554147049

- Reported issues on mantrasongs versions mod-page should be fixed.

There is also the add-on mod [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2141107008]Zen Garden Plus[/url] by velcroboy333 that lets you use the plants in this mod in different recipes for food and beverages.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/ZenGarden][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
This mod adds various zen and rock garden themed decorations. Researching stonecutting unlocks everything.

[h1]Items Added:[/h1]
[b]Cherry Wood:[/b] Pink colored wood
[b]Ebony Wood:[/b] Black colored wood
[b]Zen Cherries:[/b] Secondary resource of the Zen Cherry Tree
[b]Persimmon:[/b] Secondary resource of the Persimmon Tree
[b]Crabapple:[/b] Secondary resource of the Crabapple Tree

[h1]Objects Added:[/h1]
[b]Border Path:[/b] A nice looking border for placing along important paths, hallways, farms, etc.
[b]Border Pond:[/b] Similar to the border path, but with water
[b]Border Path Pillar:[/b] A pillar made to fit along a border path or border pond. Can be used to support roofs.
[b]Stacked Rocks:[/b] A series of stacked rocks, available in two sizes.
[b]Artificial Hedge:[/b] Decorative hedges. Colonists can pass through them.
[b]Tall Hedge:[/b] A hedge grown for decorative purposes.
[b]Dense Grass:[/b] Tall, thick grass grown to hide the dirt ground.
[b]Half Wall:[/b] A simple stone half wall, can be built with or without powered lanterns.
[b]Flower arch:[/b] Used to decorate paths or wedding spots. Vines grow when it's not too cold, and flowers bloom in the spring and summer seasons
[b]Scenic Bench:[/b] Bench for colonists to sit at that gains beauty based on surroundings. Additional beauty is calculated for plants, water, and rivers.
[b]Fountain:[/b] A decorative fountain of water, available in two sizes.
[b]Standing Lantern:[/b] Decorative lantern for indoor areas.
[b]Pedestal Lantern:[/b] Outdoors powered lantern for garden areas.
[b]Zen Cherry Tree:[/b] A vibrant and colorful tree often grown for decoration. Produces zen cherries in the spring and summer. Can also be chopped down for cherrywood.
[b]Persimmon Tree:[/b] A hardwood tree well known for its delicious soft fruit and uniquely dark heartwood. Produces persimmons in the fall and winter. Can also be chopped down for ebony wood.
[b]Crabapple Tree:[/b] A colorful hardwood tree which grows small apples. Produces crabapples in the summer and fall. Can also be chopped down for wood.

[h1]Other Features:[/h1]
[b]Orchard Zone:[/b] Growing zone that prevents plants from being harvested, and instead allows harvesting of the secondary resources.
[b]Rough Gravel:[/b] Cheaper gravel flooring that cannot be raked. May be found in the world as paths
[b]Gravel Floor:[/b] A simple gravel floor that can be raked into vertical, horizontal, or curved patterns - or left unraked

[h1]Save Compatability[/h1]
This mod can be added to existing saves.
Always back up your saves before adding new mods as there is always the possibility for issues.

[h1]Mod Compatability[/h1]
[b]Architect Sense:[/b] All gravel floors grouped together 
[b]Kura's Extra Minerals:[/b] Gravel floors for stone types that do not overlap Cupro's Stones
[b]Cupro's Stones:[/b] Gravel floors for stone types
[b]Medieval Times:[/b] Desk requires Cherry Wood (based on description)
[b]Survivalist's Additions:[/b] Saguaro Cactus can be grown in an Orchard Zone to produce Prickly Pear; Cherries, Persimmon, and Crabapple can be used to make Vinegar 
[b]SeedsPlease:[/b] Seeds added for orchard trees 

[hr]
[h1]mantrasongs description[/h1]
Adds decorative garden stuff.

ORIGINAL AUTHOR: cuproPanda

This is a 1.0 port of Zen Garden by cuproPanda. I am NOT the creator, all credit is attributed to cuproPanda. Please report any issues as they come up.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]</description>
</ModMetaData>